callersmart.com 2019-05-31

# Privacy Policy - CallerSmart

**Effective Date: December 1, 2016**

Thank you for downloading our application ("App") or visiting our website, located at www.CallerSmart.com ("Site" or "Website"). This policy covers how the information you enter into our Site or App is handled by our Company. Both the Site and App are property of Caller Smart Inc. ("Company ," "We" or "Us").

We have created this privacy policy ("Privacy Policy") in order to disclose our information gathering and dissemination practices, specifically as it relates to your use of the Site or App. This policy does not apply to the practices of companies that we do not own or control or to people that we do not employ or manage.

We understand the importance that Internet users place on privacy and have designed our Site and App with this in mind. That's why We do not rent, sell, share, or trade your personal information with third parties other than as disclosed within this Privacy Policy.

In general, We reserves the right to release current or past Site or App data: (a) in the event that we believe that the Site or App is being or has been used in violation of this Privacy Policy, the Terms and Conditions, or to commit unlawful acts; (b) as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site or App; or (c) if Company is sold or acquired.

While Company strongly encourages clients and partners to adopt responsible approaches to online marketing, Company is not responsible for the information practices of third-parties. The collection, use and disclosure of information by clients, partners, and any other third party is subject to their respective privacy policies, which may differ from this Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

When you visit the Site or use our App, we send a cookie ("Cookie") to assign an anonymous, unique identifier to your Internet browser. Thereafter, We may access our Cookies on your computer or mobile device. This helps enhance your experience with Us, and in many instances is necessary for the provision of the services offered on the Site or in the App.

We use Cookies to store your passwords, so that you do not have to enter it more than once and to enhance your experience on the Site and in our App. We do not link the information we store in Cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our Site or in our App.

To find out more about Cookies, please visit [www.cookiecentral.com](http://www.cookiecentral.com/ "Cookie Central"). To disable and reject certain Cookies, please reference the above website for specific browser disabling information. Please be advised that where you disable or reject Cookies, you may not be able to use certain services offered through the Site or App. Furthermore, We reserve the right to retain Cookie data indefinitely.

In addition, We allow third-party companies to collect certain information when you visit our Website or use our App. These companies may utilize their own cookies, pixels or other technologies to collect and use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., hashed data, click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit the websites of the Digital Advertising Alliance at [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/ "Digital Advertising Alliance \(DAA\)") and Networking Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices/](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/#completed "Network Advertising Initiative").

## Clear GIFs

In addition to Cookies, our third party tracking utility company may employ a software technology called clear GIFs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs) and collects usage data.

Clear GIFs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. They help us better manage content on our Site or in our App by informing us what content is effective with our users.

In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, clear GIFs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence.

We do not tie the information gathered by clear GIFs to personally identifiable information.

## Use of Information Obtained by Company

Any personal information that you submit at the Site or in our App remains your property. However, by submitting that information to us, you grant to us the right to use your personal information, subject to applicable state and federal law, in the ways set forth herein.

We will send you service-related announcements when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature.

Based upon the personally identifiable information you provide us, we will send you a welcome email to verify your email address. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide the services you request, and to manage your account. These communications will be handled with you via email.

We may employ other companies and individuals to perform certain functions on our behalf. Examples include sending electronic mail, removing duplicate information from user lists, analyzing data, and providing marketing analysis. The agents performing these limited functions on Our behalf shall have access to your personal information as needed, strictly in the performance of their functions. We do not permit them to use your personal information for other purposes.

We will use your personal information for customer service, to provide you with information that you may request, to customize your experience on the Site or in our App and/or to contact you when necessary in connection with your activities on the Site or in the App. We will also display personally-identifiable information of yours to other users who specifically request it by entering your phone number.

With your consent, we may upload your phone's address book to Our servers, including detailed contact information for your contacts. By consenting to this optional feature, we will periodically sync and store your contacts to help you and others identify mystery phone calls and texts. You can stop sharing and delete all of your stored contacts imported from your phone on Our at any time via our App.

We may also use your personal information for internal business purposes, such as analyzing and managing our business. We may also combine the information we have gathered about you with information from other sources. We may use third parties to help us operate our business or administer activities on the Site or in the App.

We reserve the right to share personally identifiable information in connection with the sale, merger, consolidation, change in control, transfer of substantial assets or reorganization or liquidation of Company. Company may release account and any other personally identifiable information: (i) to respond to a subpoena or otherwise comply with the law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Site or in our App; (ii) to enforce or apply this Privacy Policy, the Terms and Conditions and other Company agreements and policies; (iii) when we deem it necessary or appropriate including, without limitation, sharing your e-mail address with other third parties for suppression purposes in compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act of 2003, as amended from time to time, and Federal Trade Commission implementing regulations; (iv) to other users who first request personally-identifiable information of yours such as the name, address, and likeness associated with a phone number; and/or (v) to protect the rights, property or safety of Company or others, including exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection purposes. Without limiting the generality of the foregoing, we will share the personal information with our third party data, marketing, and sales partners for the purpose of sending you marketing emails.

We may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes. If you wish to end your e-mail subscription from a particular list, please follow the instructions at the end of each e-mail message to unsubscribe from that particular list. In every e-mail communication that Company sends, there is an unsubscribe hyperlink that allows the recipient to unsubscribe from the specific marketing program by simply clicking the hyperlink provided and following the instructions that follow.

## Data Retention

In order to to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements, Company will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services.

## Changes in Our Privacy Policy

If we change our Privacy Policy, we will prominently post a link to those changes on our Site's homepage and in our App so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, by means of a notice on our Site's home page, or by means of a notice inside our App.

Your continued use of the Site or App and/or continued receipt of Company e-mails after posting of the Privacy Policy change on the Site or App, or receipt of a Privacy Policy change notification e-mail, as applicable, constitutes an affirmative acknowledgment and acceptance by you of the modified Privacy Policy.

## Security

While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us, and you do so at your own risk.

## E-mail Choice

Your email address is used primarily for password recovery. In addition, we provide you with the option to opt-out from receiving information sent via electronic mailings from us. You may unsubscribe from receiving e-mail at any time by following the instructions contained at the end of every e-mailing.

We may maintain separate e-mail lists for different purposes, such as one for password recovery and one for marketing. If you wish to remove your e-mail subscription from a particular list, you need to follow the instructions at the end of each e-mail message to automatically unsubscribe from that particular list.

Be aware that information sent on behalf of third party advertisers is prepared several days in advance, so you may continue to receive e-mail from us for up to ten (10) days following the unsubscribe procedures detailed above.

## Links

The Site or App contains links to other websites and services. Please be aware that Company is not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage you to be aware when you leave the Site or App and to read the privacy policies of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by Us.

## Blog

We offer a publicly accessible blog. You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them. To request removal of your personal information from our blog, contact us at feedback@callersmart.com. In some cases, we may not be able to remove your personal information, in which case we will let you know if we are unable to do so and why.

## Children's Privacy

We are very sensitive to the issue of children's privacy and, therefore, we endeavor to protect the privacy of children using the Internet.

The Site and App, as well as its products and services, are not developed for or directed at children. Visitors under eighteen (18) years of age are not eligible to do business with us and we do not knowingly solicit or collect personal information from any person that we actually know is under the age of eighteen (18).

Company encourages parents and guardians to spend time online with their children and to participate and monitor the interactive activities of their children.If you believe that your child has provided Company with any personally identifiable information, please e-mail feedback@callersmart.com to have this information removed.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of the Site or App, or your dealings with the Site or App, please contact us at feedback@callersmart.com.

Mailing Address: Caller Smart Inc., 308 East 5th Ave., Vancouver B.C. V5T 1H4
